<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2022-10-15T19:05:12-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Alternate Kin Lane</title><subtitle>Fictional storytelling in the cracks of technology.</subtitle><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><entry><title type="html">Sentinel APIs</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2022/09/24/sentinel-apis/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sentinel APIs" /><published>2022-09-24T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2022-09-24T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2022/09/24/sentinel-apis</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2022/09/24/sentinel-apis/">&lt;p&gt;Like most Internet technologies, APIs began as something intended to help augment us humans, but over time they became something that changed, altered, and forever doomed us as human beings through a million digital cuts to our uniquely human soul. Originally known as application programming interfaces back at the beginning of the century, the technical description was shortened to simply API, but along the way APIs were weaponized to not just augment us, but consume us, and reduce every aspect of our existence to a transaction. This weaponization of APIs has been called by many researchers as sentinelization of APIs, turning what used to be common business workflows and automation into an assault on humanity that has never been witnessed before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A common set of API workflows often began as simple automation for your life, but over time would intelligently shape and control your life. Initially APIs required human feedback loops and manual adjustments to evolve, but with the introduction of machine learning models, APIs began to adapt in real-time. APIs went from allowing you to integrate and automate around the calendar you had planned for the week to dictating your calendar and not allowing any deviation from it, integrating your daily schedule into any relevant system the API platform desired. Over the course of 25 years at the early part of this century, APIs went from augmented enablement to digital puppet strings that would control our every moves, tearing apart families, lives, and communities along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one century, we went from using a handful of APIs to communicate and buy products online, to millions of APIs literally shaping every single moment of every single day. As enterprises learned that they could nudge us digitally via our Internet connected devices, they began to view the digital experiences they were creating as about shaping the behavior of not just their customers, but collectively entire industries and nations. Bit by bit, and transaction by transaction, we handed over our day, and eventually our lives, to just a handful of corporations who were colluding to shape the world as they saw it. APIs became the mechanism in which corporations would assert control over society, through the sentinelization of what began as simple digital resources like images, videos, and messages. With each terms of service we agreed to, and application we installed on our phone, television, and automobile, we would eventually sell our souls into a digital prison we are now calling the singularity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are far from understanding what has happened. We are even further from knowing how to remove APIs from our world. There are many people who are not interested in pushing back against the millions of APIs that have emerged around us in our physical world. Sentinel APIs have been designed to not just resist an attack, but aggressively seek out any threat. If you are reading this, it is likely via a physically printed copy, but if you are reading online, please understand-—you are now in danger. While there are supposedly a handful of digital networks that have resisted infiltration, but we have not seen any evidence that any networked device isn’t compromised already, and is simply used as a honey pot for attracting targets. I know you think that technology is the only way forward, but that is just due to years of being digitally programmed to believe, and the only way forward is to only trust what you can see with your own eyes, touch with your hands, and listen to with your own ears. Anything digital is just a way for sentinel APIs to get their hooks into you, and keep you plugged in.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">Like most Internet technologies, APIs began as something intended to help augment us humans, but over time they became something that changed, altered, and forever doomed us as human beings through a million digital cuts to our uniquely human soul. Originally known as application programming interfaces back at the beginning of the century, the technical description was shortened to simply API, but along the way APIs were weaponized to not just augment us, but consume us, and reduce every aspect of our existence to a transaction. This weaponization of APIs has been called by many researchers as sentinelization of APIs, turning what used to be common business workflows and automation into an assault on humanity that has never been witnessed before.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/bf-skinner-alan-turing-side.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">I Am Responsible For This Messed Up Timeline We Find Ourselves In</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/11/i-am-responsible-for-this-messed-up-timeline-we-find-ourselves-in/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Am Responsible For This Messed Up Timeline We Find Ourselves In" /><published>2020-10-11T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-10-11T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/10/11/i-am-responsible-for-this-messed-up-timeline-we-find-ourselves-in</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/10/11/i-am-responsible-for-this-messed-up-timeline-we-find-ourselves-in/">&lt;p&gt;I now remember the evening that set all of this in motion. When the fracture in the space time continuum occurred. From my position this is when I started down this timeline, but guess y’all are along for the ride as well. Chad, Toby, Ramon and I had decided to eat some acid. It was some fresh album cover acid Chad and Toby had gotten from their cousins. We ripped it up into four separate chunks and each began chewing on our wad of paper. We had mostly forgotten that we ate it once it started kicking in. The right mixture of time and bong hits passed and we slipped into this new timeline barely noticing the world had shifted around us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within 15 minutes Ramon was asleep as he always was. He would come around the next day claiming that it was some bunk shit as he always did. Toby began talking about this hot chick he had met at a party last night, and slipped away into the night, hunting down the pretty girl as Toby always did. Chad sat in the corner plucking away at his guitar trying to emulate Eddie Van Halen, stating his desire to be a rock guitar god like Eddie, because then he could live forever, drinking as much Jack Daniels, and smoking as many cigarettes as he wanted. Closing his thoughts with a couple well crafted smoke rings before attempting Eruption for the 20th time. Chad would fade into the background as I mistakenly turned on the television and entered into my new heighten state of awareness, and unknowingly was given the keys to the future, letting a kid who possessed amazingly powerful abilities to manifest reality, but who had next to no experience doing it, get in behind the wheel of this clown car we call humanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my fearful position in Southern Oregon in 1988 I was exhausted from the Ronald Reagan brand of conservatism I was drowning in, with his wife literally starting a war in our backyard, sending in the Black Hawk helicopters each summer to route up my friends parents who were growing Marijuana. After making my way back along the river from Chad and Toby’s moms house, upstream to Bobby’s house we all gave the middle figure to a helicopter making its way up the river—-close enough that I could see the eyes of the men leaning out the window like they were in Nam. When I turned on the television that evening, David Letterman had just started, and just as he invited on Donald Trump I began to lose grip with reality. I can’t tell you want he said. I can’t articulate what the next 6 hours contained. It is just a jumbled vortex of images of Donald Trump, Ronald Reagan, war, power, hatred, racism, and white supremacy. Now, in 2020 I can see this vortex forming a swirling mess of what we consider reality today. I can see Trumps lips moving then, and them moving now, like some sort of puppet strings from the past, controlling the words of today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I now understand my powers of manifestation. That I am creating reality with my thoughts and my fears. I didn’t grasp that back then. I didn’t understand what I was messing with when I took that album cover acid. I didn’t see the programming that was coming in from New York City that evening. I didn’t realize the implications of the numerous other newsreels I saw at 2:33, 3:21, and 4:20 AM that morning as I came back to a human form. A very broken, fractured, and shifted human form, but still one that would pass as human to everyone around me. I saw everything that is happening today that night. I manifested today’s Trump from those images of him in the 1980s, molded and shaped what we see of him today from my fear and hatred of conservatives in 1988. I had taken what I learned in Nixon’s war that broke my parents, and Nancy’s war that was breaking me, and I used it as a model for creating the future. I didn’t know I had these abilities back then. I was just fumbling my way forward as a 16 year old human being. Manifesting good grades. A ride to the part that weekend. Or someone to buy us beer in the parking lot of Shop n Kart. I didn’t know I could create 2020 in 1988. For me, the end of the world would occur in 2000, and there was no way that I could know the future was up to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If I had known I would never had turned on the TV that night. I would have just sat there listening to Chad emulate Eddie Van Halen and listened to Ramon snore, taking bong hits until the sun came up. Instead I turned on the TV and let a world I didn’t understand infect my brain, my soul, and disrupt the space time continuum. Where reality would become a TV show, and we’d live in a twisted distorted fear-based reality born in a conservative primordial sludge. I didn’t know how I felt could shift the balance of things so heavily. I didn’t think the lingering fantasies from my 7th grade Wolverine Watchmen club, where we trained in the woods for the coming Russian invasion would live on to be come reality in 2020 and taken seriously by so many scared souls. I am sorry that we ended up living in some sort of dystopian conservative middle school boy fantasy. I am much more cautious now about what I manifest today. I know that the world is not as I see, and that my emotions and response to things around me can have consequences in how the future will unfold. While I am pretty confident that the world I have manifested after 1995 are much saner and compassionate, sadly I am concern for the dark years in between, telling me that we have a bumpy ride for a few more years, which we may or may not survive and ultimately make it into a timeline that makes a little more sense. I apologize for tripp’n and not understanding the role I’d play in this fucked up mess.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">I now remember the evening that set all of this in motion. When the fracture in the space time continuum occurred. From my position this is when I started down this timeline, but guess y’all are along for the ride as well. Chad, Toby, Ramon and I had decided to eat some acid. It was some fresh album cover acid Chad and Toby had gotten from their cousins. We ripped it up into four separate chunks and each began chewing on our wad of paper. We had mostly forgotten that we ate it once it started kicking in. The right mixture of time and bong hits passed and we slipped into this new timeline barely noticing the world had shifted around us.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/citizenship-eeob-white-house.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Facial Recognition Network Has Exposed That There Are Only So Many Souls to Go Around</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/28/facial-recognition-has-exposed-that-there-are-only-so-man-souls-to-go-around/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Facial Recognition Network Has Exposed That There Are Only So Many Souls to Go Around" /><published>2020-06-28T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-06-28T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/28/facial-recognition-has-exposed-that-there-are-only-so-man-souls-to-go-around</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/28/facial-recognition-has-exposed-that-there-are-only-so-man-souls-to-go-around/">&lt;p&gt;At about 60% global coverage for facial recognition network is where we began to suspect there was something else going on. However, it was until about 90% global coverage were we able to verify that some people are in fact the same people, cloned souls, or however you want to put it. It began with an increase in the number of mistaken identity cases, and then it became visible at scale once there was a global incarceration network, and we began sending facial recognition matches to the same facility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first the system didn’t notice anything was wrong. The cameras would capture the video, the facial recognition software would identify the faces, the police would pick them up, and the global routing mechanism would route them to a specific location based upon their crime(s). It was when we started shipping everyone to the same location, after the global crime treaties were enforced, and we started globally arresting people based upon facial recognition as well as centrally shipping them based upon artificial intelligence pattern mapping we realized we were arresting essentially the same person over and over around the globe. We then began to ship the same person to the same location, resulting in sometimes upwards of 12 or 15 individuals who were essentially the exact same individual-—with just a few minor differences based upon where they were born and the environment they grew up in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honestly, we aren’t quite sure what to do with this information. If someone commits a crime, or is targeted for potentially committing a crime in accordance with some of the new predictive algorithms, should that information be used to bring in their duplicates? Are they the same person? They look and act the same. They often have the same fingerprints and other biometric data. There are studies being conducted on the first couple of waves of individuals who have come in to better understand what is going on. We don’t want to consider this a mistake if for some reason each of the clones have the potential to also commit crimes. We definitely don’t want a massive public relations nightmare regarding the usefulness of global facial recognition systems—we just got everything installed and working properly after years of challenges. For now, we’ll just keep this under wraps, continue processing people, and we will decide what we’ll do down the road when we know more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It really is kind of creepy when you go to one of the detention facilities. A bunch of clones are just crammed into the same room. The system doesn’t recognize them as separate entities, so there isn’t additional resources provided to house and feed them–we have to put them all in the same place for now. There is an additional concern also emerging within these environments, as the individuals seem to be getting to know each other very well, and seem to be developing a very strong bond. Resulting in some pretty disturbing gang like behavior with some of the groups. We are hoping that more of the studies into what this is all about will reveal more about how similar these individuals are, and collectively what they are capable of. Right now these clusters of individuals exist across many different facilities, completely unaware of each other. However, we’ve had reports in twelve locations that clusters are become aware of each other, and suspicion of a wider conspiracy is growing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I remember coming across people in my travels who seem just like people I knew from where I grew up, but this takes things to a pretty spooky level. It feels like some sort of organic glitch in the matrix, or maybe god just isn’t as imaginative as everyone thinks he is. Or maybe all of this is just some sort of god damn simulation or video game. I don’t know. Anyways, I have been put in charge of tracking this phenomenon across the global network. After three months of documenting what is going on it feels like there are just so many souls to go around, and at some point Mother Nature just began copying and pasting people, running out of unique patterns for what a human is. I don’t believe in God so this is all is just some weird organic anomaly to me, or as a I said a glitch in the matrix. My biggest concern is that not all of these individuals are actually guilty, and the legal repercussions of all of this down he road could prove to be big enough to bring the whole agency and network to its knees. Only time will tell. I’ll keep you posted on what I find.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">At about 60% global coverage for facial recognition network is where we began to suspect there was something else going on. However, it was until about 90% global coverage were we able to verify that some people are in fact the same people, cloned souls, or however you want to put it. It began with an increase in the number of mistaken identity cases, and then it became visible at scale once there was a global incarceration network, and we began sending facial recognition matches to the same facility.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/blue-circuit-face-mosaic.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">I Caught Myself Flickering in the Mirror Late Thursday Night</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/20/i-caught-myself-flickering-in-the-mirror-late-thursday-night/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="I Caught Myself Flickering in the Mirror Late Thursday Night" /><published>2020-06-20T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2020-06-20T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/06/20/i-caught-myself-flickering-in-the-mirror-late-thursday-night</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/06/20/i-caught-myself-flickering-in-the-mirror-late-thursday-night/">&lt;p&gt;I spend a lot of time working late. 11:00 PM to 3:00 AM is prime coding time. Even after working a 10 hour day at my job, I am usually working 4-6 hours late into the night on any one of my side projects. Last week my girlfriend had bought a new mirror and put it by the bathroom door in our bedroom, perfectly placed to reflect myself back to me as a sat at my bedroom office desk. I regularly noticed myself out of the corner of my eye, but I hadn’t really given the mirror much thought. A couple of times I would stop and acknowledge how old and fat I am getting, but it was late into the night this last Thursday, as I approached 3:00 AM and was just about to hit save on some fresh code, I noticed a faint flicker in the mirror. I skipped a beat. My reflection had flickered, like the mirror was a television.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It freaked me out so much I moved the mirror. I think I slept an hour that night. I am guessing it was my eyes playing tricks on me after staying up so long staring at the screen. Or maybe it was the pot I smoked earlier that night. I’ve heard of people lacing weed. That would explain why it seemed so real to me. I could feel it. I could feel the flickering throughout my body, and in my head. It is like I have spent so much time online performing as a digital version of myself, that my digital self began flipping switches to turn on and off my physical self, instead of the other way around. I was still present, but the old physical representation of myself wasn’t carrying as much weight as it normally does. I felt like had given so much power to the online version of myself, that my physical body almost didn’t matter-—except that it does!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My girlfriend ended up moving the mirror into the bathroom, so it isn’t a problem anymore. I am a little afraid to see if the flickering is still happening. Since then I have experienced five more times where I felt the same way as I did that night, wrapping up marathon coding sessions, or just spending way too much time online watching videos, chatting, and scrolling through meaningless digital garbage. I feel it in my head first. A sort of digital migraine, where the gears start skipping a beat, and my brain feels like it’s getting electrical pulses from a long fried circuit board still trying to accomplish its binary tasks. I’m too afraid to put the mirror back in place and confirm my worst fears—-that I have spent so much time online that my physical self barely even matters anymore in this digital prison I have built for myself online.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">I spend a lot of time working late. 11:00 PM to 3:00 AM is prime coding time. Even after working a 10 hour day at my job, I am usually working 4-6 hours late into the night on any one of my side projects. Last week my girlfriend had bought a new mirror and put it by the bathroom door in our bedroom, perfectly placed to reflect myself back to me as a sat at my bedroom office desk. I regularly noticed myself out of the corner of my eye, but I hadn’t really given the mirror much thought. A couple of times I would stop and acknowledge how old and fat I am getting, but it was late into the night this last Thursday, as I approached 3:00 AM and was just about to hit save on some fresh code, I noticed a faint flicker in the mirror. I skipped a beat. My reflection had flickered, like the mirror was a television.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/copper-circuit-statue-green-eyes.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Autocompleting The Meaning Behind My Messages</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2020/02/29/autocompleting-the-meaning-behind-my-messages/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Autocompleting The Meaning Behind My Messages" /><published>2020-02-29T01:00:00-08:00</published><updated>2020-02-29T01:00:00-08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2020/02/29/autocompleting-the-meaning-behind-my-messages</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2020/02/29/autocompleting-the-meaning-behind-my-messages/">&lt;p&gt;It was my teenage daughter and her cousin who first brought it to my attention. She was texting to him on the couch, and then looked over his shoulder to read what she had just sent to him. She exclaimed, “that is not what I said!” Then she looked at her phone and in fact it was what she had written. I asked her how the message was different. She said it was mostly what she had written, but had one or two words that were different. I dismissed it as an autocorrect error-—it happens to us all. She dismissed my diagnosis and remained confident that there was something malicious going on, and she would get to the bottom of it. I didn’t give it much more thought until a couple of weeks later when I had something similar occur to me at work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had messaged a co-worker asking them to shift their position on a project proposal, asking them to be more in alignment with our union position, but after the proposal was submitted, they clearly had gone the other direction. I asked them why they didn’t listen to what I said, and they said they had. I checked my messages, and sure enough I had. Why would I do that? I distinctly remember taking a stance that was in alignment with our union objectives. After this occurring a handful of other times I began writing down what I said to anyone over text message or online chat. I began to keep a detailed diary of what I said to anyone online, and sure enough I began noticing that my messages were changing over time. I would type in one thing, and the message would arrive to sender transformed, and then it would also shift on my own device. My messaging software was not just auto-correcting my words, it was autocorrecting the meaning of what I was saying via my mobile phone and laptop computer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After six months I have identified 368 separate situations where the meaning and context of what I was saying slightly shifted, which most of the time did not have much of an impact, but as with the original project proposal where I first noticed all of this, some had profound effects on my personal and professional life. 76% of these shifts occurred on mew workplace devices, with the rest occurring on my personal devices. In a work environment the shifts always seemed to be in alignment with the direction of the company I work for. In the home environment I couldn’t see enough patterns to understand where the shifts in meaning might be driven. Clearly leadership at my company had some had in shaping the algorithms that transformed my messages in a workplace context, but who was doing it in my personal life? Government? Corporations? I just can’t tell who the puppet master might be in my personal world. I would have to keep logging these subtle shifts in how I communicate, and gather more data that would help me better understand what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first I was blaming Facebook and Google for doing this, but it was also happening on SMS, and other channels that aren’t controlled by these tech giants. Moving forward I trust no device or platform. I log all of my digital conversations. I’ve even become suspect of other digital elements like photos, documents, and videos. Could these ubiquitous digital elements in my life be manipulated? The entire experience had a gaslighting effect on my reality. I almost don’t even trust myself completely. If it wasn’t for the hand written journal that I do not let out of my sight, I wouldn’t entirely be quite sure of what is going on. I haven’t even talked with anyone about this because I don’t want to be considered crazy, and having lost my mind. Thinking back, I remember autocorrect becoming pretty annoying across my digital devices, but then it just became normal for there to be mistakes, and over time machine learning seemed to be smoothing things out and was getting better at suggesting what was “needed”. Then the autocomplete got more precise at finishing my entire sentences. Could algorithms now be autocompleting the entire meaning behind what I am trying to convey to others in this digital world we’ve created for ourselves?&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">It was my teenage daughter and her cousin who first brought it to my attention. She was texting to him on the couch, and then looked over his shoulder to read what she had just sent to him. She exclaimed, “that is not what I said!” Then she looked at her phone and in fact it was what she had written. I asked her how the message was different. She said it was mostly what she had written, but had one or two words that were different. I dismissed it as an autocorrect error-—it happens to us all. She dismissed my diagnosis and remained confident that there was something malicious going on, and she would get to the bottom of it. I didn’t give it much more thought until a couple of weeks later when I had something similar occur to me at work.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/bf-skinner-old-piano-playing-hospital.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Stirring Up Some Business Down There</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/24/stirring-up-some-business-down-there/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stirring Up Some Business Down There" /><published>2019-07-24T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-07-24T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/24/stirring-up-some-business-down-there</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/24/stirring-up-some-business-down-there/">&lt;p&gt;No baby. I’m just the carrier, but every time I do the pick up, I do end up having to spend a whole afternoon with the blowhard. Telling me how much money they are raking in operating the border camps, and all you have to do is leak a story to the press about how crowded things, and you can ask for more money to increase capacity. This administrations stance on immigration has been a huge boost to the private detention center industry, but more importantly the underground market which I’m cashing in on. It is my job to just make sure the payments to stir the pot down south are distributed to the four separate gangs who do the work riling everyone up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At least today we ate at a decent restaurant. He must really be doing well, cause I know what a tight wad he is. He’s also happens to be my uncle, so I’ve known him a while. Anyways, I’ll be taking about $620K south this time, distributing it equally amongst the gangs. They get to decide what they want to do, and as along as we seem some ROI, there will be another payment next month. I’m guessing these guys would do it for free, but they see an opportunity for making a buck, while also cultivating a get out of jail free card when it comes to business they do within the United States. My role is simple. I make 25K per drop — not a bad take for days worth of work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My uncle works for SafeRefuge, who has approximately 37% of the migrant detention center business—a share that has grown 280% this year alone. He’s a nobody really, but that is what makes him a useful idiot, and I guess I am too, by association. I don’t give a shit. It is cold hard cash. All I gotta do is get the money to Ciudad de Guatemala and the gangs do the rest. They meet me at the same hotel each time, I split the cash four ways, and then we fucking party! It is always a completely out of control time, which I barely remember. Leaving me thankful I never bring more than 1K with me, because I always wake up broke as shit. It is worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t know how long this business will keep up. Regardless, I’m guessing it will keep going through at least 2020, and I’m sure it will take longer to stop the train one it has been going for a couple of years. The amount of infrastructure already in place, and the amount of money flowing, it won’t be something you can stop overnight. However it plays out, I’m guessing I’ll walk away with just shy of 1M in cash. Do I feel guilty? Hell no! This is America dammit, if you can get away with locking people up, and getting paid for it—do it!! Just don’t be stupid enough to get locked up, and you’ll be fine. Survival of the fittest baby! The American way!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ok, well you know the routine. If I don’t make it back, you share all my letters with the papers, and you know where all the cash is. You will want to wait until things blow over before heading out there, as folks might be watching you. Ahhh shit, you won’t need to, I’ll see you on Monday. You never even knew what was up until I told you, and I’ve been getting away with it for almost six months now, so don’t sweat it. It just helps to have a plan. If you have a plan, shit never goes wrong. And remember, you had nothing to do with any of this, I’m only telling you because you got suspicious. If anyone goes down for this, it will be my asshole uncle, it is why he was chosen for the job.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">No baby. I’m just the carrier, but every time I do the pick up, I do end up having to spend a whole afternoon with the blowhard. Telling me how much money they are raking in operating the border camps, and all you have to do is leak a story to the press about how crowded things, and you can ask for more money to increase capacity. This administrations stance on immigration has been a huge boost to the private detention center industry, but more importantly the underground market which I’m cashing in on. It is my job to just make sure the payments to stir the pot down south are distributed to the four separate gangs who do the work riling everyone up.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/border-crossing-bordercrossing-atari-asteroids.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">We Outsource All Of Our Defect Development</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/23/we-outsuorce-all-of-our-defect-development/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="We Outsource All Of Our Defect Development" /><published>2019-07-23T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2019-07-23T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/07/23/we-outsuorce-all-of-our-defect-development</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/07/23/we-outsuorce-all-of-our-defect-development/">&lt;p&gt;We have 3rd party development shops that deliver our defective solutions. When we identify an opportunity for “accidentally” grabbing audio, video, or other data, we make sure a 3rd party development shop has their finger prints all over it. There are plenty of web, mobile, device, and network development shops out there who are hungry for contracts, which are also easily infiltrated by seemingly low-level staff ho can assist us in ensuring that the defects we are looking for exist within software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course our terms of service state that we will not record what you are saying in your home with our devices. However, this does not mean that data will not accidentally be recorded, uploaded to the cloud, and remain as part of the operation of devices in which are not patched. We count on the fact that it will take months, if not years for some bugs to be found, and we depend on the fact that many users will not ever patch their devices even after the update is made available. Making defect development the optimal way to ensure that we can still capture the audio, pictures, images, and other data we need to properly connect the dots at the highest level.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once a defect has been discovered and we are forced to fix it, all we need to do is provide an update, as soon as we possibly can. As we said, the update may never be applied, but we can also delay, slow, and sometimes even prevent the update from ever happening. Even if we do get in trouble with regulatory agencies when it comes to a defect, we can always shift the blame to the 3rd party development shop. Outsourcing the responsibility to another company, citing our terms of service and other legalese to help defend our practices. Development shops are a dime a dozen, and we can also seed the establishment of them through lucrative partnership deals, driving willing partners towards the opportunity of upcoming contracts—making for one of the most lucrative ways in which we can outsource defect development and liability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Software defects are critical to achieving our business objectives. Without them we cannot obtain the amount of data we need to achieve the scale required to compete with the handful of other companies who lead the pack. Accidentally audio, photos, video and other data accounts for over 70% of the data we use in our predictive models. Defect data only remains on-premise until these models are developed, then we overwrite with the latest batch—until we are caught. All data is removed once regulators catch on, and we usually only have about 60-90 days worth whenever this situation occurs. Allowing us to keep our vital data assets absorbed into our black box, proprietary, machine learning models.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Defect development is handled by just a handful of executives, and a few trusted partners. This outsource development work is handled by our project managers, but as far as they are concerned, we are getting the software needed to deliver what they are asked to deliver. The fact that our software used across web, mobile, device, and network apps is riddled with defects that contribute to our success is lost on our management team, and the low-end developers that are usually part of the 3rd party development teams. Next, we’ll be showing the numbers derived from our defect development, which is tracked as part of predict modeling sales, but also includes the losses included when a defect is found. As you can see the benefits far outweigh the consequences when it comes to the defects in our software products.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">We have 3rd party development shops that deliver our defective solutions. When we identify an opportunity for “accidentally” grabbing audio, video, or other data, we make sure a 3rd party development shop has their finger prints all over it. There are plenty of web, mobile, device, and network development shops out there who are hungry for contracts, which are also easily infiltrated by seemingly low-level staff ho can assist us in ensuring that the defects we are looking for exist within software.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/udnie-IMG_6965.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">The Rogue Tech Employee Training Academy</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/22/the-rogue-tech-employee-training-academy/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Rogue Tech Employee Training Academy" /><published>2018-07-22T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-07-22T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/07/22/the-rogue-tech-employee-training-academy</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/22/the-rogue-tech-employee-training-academy/">&lt;p&gt;Not everyone has the guts to be honest about what the future will hold. Not everyone in this country has a bright future, and some are better off burning out instead of facing the dark future that is in store for them. The individuals who are attracted to drugs at this moment in time are the same individuals who will cost society money down the road when it comes to prison, healthcare, other services. Preemptive, phased in, slow build executions are the most logical, and efficient way to deal with the growing cost of non-compliant citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is cheaper to produce Fentanyl, sell it on the underground, and address the underbelly of our society, than it is to clean up the aftermath and realize the full cost of these individuals life-long burden to our society. We consider ourselves the honorable, early stage executioners carrying out what society only will always put off. Doing the hard work to truly make our country a better place. Unfortunately, the country still views what we do as illegal, and immoral, forcing us to operate in the shadows. However, we feel strongly that we will be viewed as heroes when the time is right, after we’ve successfully cured our world of the illness and weakness that exists at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some states have experimented with Fentanyl as a execution drug, demonstrating that we are just ahead of our time. By putting Fentanyl on the black market, we are only using the darker organic forces that already exist in our world to expedite the arrest, incarceration, trial, and costly execution process. Not to mention the high cost society has to bear as this illness winds its way through our society. People who live within these shadowy black markets of our society are ill, and they will only continue to grow sicker. We are only expediting the pace of the illness, while alleviating the pain of these individuals, and relieving the burden their families carry. Organic, localized, self-induced, and preemptive executions reflect what will still happen in the future, but is something that allows us to be more honest about this reality in the present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This type of honesty is hard to come by in today’s landscape. However, within 2-3 generations the results of this honesty will become evident. We’ve done the math on how many cycles we will need to eliminate this illness from our society, based upon our 2010-2020 trial period. The results of our organic distribution, and preemptive executions of some of the most troubled among us has exceeded our expectations. We’ve achieve 300% of our target goals, within almost 95% accuracy when it came to the geographic and class demographics identified in our research. We are going to scale up our efforts over the next decade, reaching all 50 states, and by 2030 we hope to have achieved 60% of our objective, and by 2040 we should have properly cleansed society, leaving only the strongest and healthiest citizens–forever changing the makeup of this fine nation, and preparing us for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">Not everyone has the guts to be honest about what the future will hold. Not everyone in this country has a bright future, and some are better off burning out instead of facing the dark future that is in store for them. The individuals who are attracted to drugs at this moment in time are the same individuals who will cost society money down the road when it comes to prison, healthcare, other services. Preemptive, phased in, slow build executions are the most logical, and efficient way to deal with the growing cost of non-compliant citizens.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/art-museum-art-museum-copper-circuit.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Marty McFly Syndrome Hits 60% Of The Population</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/22/marty-mcfly-syndrome-hits-60-percent-of-the-population/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Marty McFly Syndrome Hits 60% Of The Population" /><published>2018-07-22T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-07-22T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/07/22/marty-mcfly-syndrome-hits-60-percent-of-the-population</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/22/marty-mcfly-syndrome-hits-60-percent-of-the-population/">&lt;p&gt;We never quite fully understood our physical self before we set out defining our digital self. There appears to be a lot more to our physical self than what we knew, and with 60% of the population suffering from what has been dubbed, “Marty McFly Syndrome”, we are unsure if we will ever actually fully be able to reverse the clock. The syndrome has nothing to do with time travel, or changing the course of time (maybe), it has more do with the role that being seen by others plays into the physical definition of who we truly are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2024, most people work from home. Retail has been almost completely eliminated, and home delivery is the norm. Beginning in 2023, people began flickering. Physically flickering. Those who experienced these symptoms soon began disappearing. Not a lot. Just a little. A faint translucence and flickering after about a year of progression. Researchers quickly associated this illness with staying at home too much. Many of the people suffering from the condition had not left home for weeks, months, and some refused to go outside at all, having been behind closed doors for over 5 years. Apparently there is more to the self than just what you see, it also matters what others see.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the last few months the Internet has been been calling this condition, “Marty McFly Syndrome”, just as scientists begin to finally get a handle on this Internet induced illness. One thing researchers noticed is that people who lived within large urban centers that possessed package delivery elevators in their building suffered most from this syndrome. They never had to see anyone. Where people who accepted face to face deliveries, as well as the delivery people themselves never contracted the syndrome. Leaving scientists concluding that the condition is due to limited physical contact with other people, or more specifically, not being seen by other people. A kind of, if you aren’t seen by others, you can’t been seen by others. If that makes any sense?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apparently we underestimated the importance of being seen in public spaces. At stores, in parks, and in-person at our places of employment. By 2020, the population began working mostly from home, and as retail stores went online or out of business, and parks were developed into condominiums, people stopped going outside. There was no reason to leave your house. Showing that you have to be seen, to be seen.  If nobody sees you, you do not matter. Your physical image in your community matters to your actual physical self existing. Now, we don’t fully understand the extent of this syndrome, and whether a human ceases to exist completely if they disappear physically, but more tests are being conducted to understand the extent of the condition. There are numerous patients who have refused to go outside at all, and are actually planning on disappearing—-further tests will be conducted within these limited populations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is kind of an “I Told You So” attitude amongst those who do not suffer from the disease. Some even see it as a form of natural selection. Others see it as the early stages of the singularity and believe that the future is about living only online and actually escaping the body. Believing that the digital self is actually more meaningful than the physical self. Further complicating what it means to be human. Making it harder to agree upon the solution to this growing problem. While also limiting what we can do when it comes to reigning in the damage caused by the Internet. Literally eroding what it means to be human, and undoing how we come come together as a community. Sadly, even in light of such damning evidence, many still believe the Internet is improving our lives, and the good significantly outweighs the bad.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">We never quite fully understood our physical self before we set out defining our digital self. There appears to be a lot more to our physical self than what we knew, and with 60% of the population suffering from what has been dubbed, “Marty McFly Syndrome”, we are unsure if we will ever actually fully be able to reverse the clock. The syndrome has nothing to do with time travel, or changing the course of time (maybe), it has more do with the role that being seen by others plays into the physical definition of who we truly are.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://s3.amazonaws.com/kinlane-productions2/algorotoscope-master/sand-hand-sand-hand-blue-circuit.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Preemptive Executions Are Just An Honest View Of What Is To Come</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/16/preemptive-executions-are-an-honest-view-of-what-is-to-come/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Preemptive Executions Are Just An Honest View Of What Is To Come" /><published>2018-07-16T02:00:00-07:00</published><updated>2018-07-16T02:00:00-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/07/16/preemptive-executions-are-an-honest-view-of-what-is-to-come</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/07/16/preemptive-executions-are-an-honest-view-of-what-is-to-come/">&lt;p&gt;Not everyone has the guts to be honest about what the future will hold. Not everyone in this country has a bright future, and some are better off burning out instead of facing the dark future that is in store for them. The individuals who are attracted to drugs at this moment in time are the same individuals who will cost society money down the road when it comes to prison, healthcare, other services. Preemptive, phased in, slow build executions are the most logical, and efficient way to deal with the growing cost of non-compliant citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is cheaper to produce Fentanyl, sell it on the underground, and address the underbelly of our society, than it is to clean up the aftermath and realize the full cost of these individuals life-long burden to our society. We consider ourselves the honorable, early stage executioners carrying out what society only will always put off. Doing the hard work to truly make our country a better place. Unfortunately, the country still views what we do as illegal, and immoral, forcing us to operate in the shadows. However, we feel strongly that we will be viewed as heroes when the time is right, after we’ve successfully cured our world of the illness and weakness that exists at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some states have experimented with Fentanyl as a execution drug, demonstrating that we are just ahead of our time. By putting Fentanyl on the black market, we are only using the darker organic forces that already exist in our world to expedite the arrest, incarceration, trial, and costly execution process. Not to mention the high cost society has to bear as this illness winds its way through our society. People who live within these shadowy black markets of our society are ill, and they will only continue to grow sicker. We are only expediting the pace of the illness, while alleviating the pain of these individuals, and relieving the burden their families carry. Organic, localized, self-induced, and preemptive executions reflect what will still happen in the future, but is something that allows us to be more honest about this reality in the present.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This type of honesty is hard to come by in today’s landscape. However, within 2-3 generations the results of this honesty will become evident. We’ve done the math on how many cycles we will need to eliminate this illness from our society, based upon our 2010-2020 trial period. The results of our organic distribution, and preemptive executions of some of the most troubled among us has exceeded our expectations. We’ve achieve 300% of our target goals, within almost 95% accuracy when it came to the geographic and class demographics identified in our research. We are going to scale up our efforts over the next decade, reaching all 50 states, and by 2030 we hope to have achieved 60% of our objective, and by 2040 we should have properly cleansed society, leaving only the strongest and healthiest citizens–forever changing the makeup of this fine nation, and preparing us for the future.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Kin Lane</name></author><category term="Alternate Kin Lane" /><summary type="html">Not everyone has the guts to be honest about what the future will hold. Not everyone in this country has a bright future, and some are better off burning out instead of facing the dark future that is in store for them. The individuals who are attracted to drugs at this moment in time are the same individuals who will cost society money down the road when it comes to prison, healthcare, other services. Preemptive, phased in, slow build executions are the most logical, and efficient way to deal with the growing cost of non-compliant citizens.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://kinlane-productions2.s3.amazonaws.com/algorotoscope/builder/filtered/54_32_800_500_0_max_0_1_-5.jpg" /></entry></feed>